I'm 42 years old My name is Andrey And
Мне 42 года Меня зовут Андрей А вам
how old are you? Your age is 30 years old 30 years old
сколько лет возраст ваш 30 лет 30 лет
I'm 30 years old Yes and your name is
Мне 30 лет Да а зовут вас
Olesya Thirty-year-old
как Олеся Тридцатилетняя
Olesya that Belarusian Belarusian
Олеся что Белорус Белорусское
name I do that
имя так делаю
T doesn't confuse at all a little
Т не смущает вообще немножко
confuses Yes a little
смущает Да чуть-чуть
hello I'm from the city of Khmelnitsky
здравствуйте Я из города Хмельницкий Вы
Where are you from?  clearly where are you from,
откуда чётко вы откуда
girl? Well,
девушка Ну
Russia, I already understand, I have no doubt
Россия я уже понял не сомневаюсь город
what city Moscow is, Moscow is a native Muscovite.
какой Москва Москва коренная москвичка А
How do you communicate?  Muscovite
чем общаешься москвичка
here I don’t
тут не
know what you need about what you need
знаю те надо о чём тебе надо у тебя
there is such an atmosphere There is pleasant music
такая Атмосфера там приятная музыка
playing
играет
she doesn’t hear you then Say it louder And
она тебя не слышит то Погромче скажи А
you say say Alisa Play the Ukrainian anthem
ты скажи скажи Алиса Включи гимн Украины
I don’t and I don’t I’m just wondering
Не я так и не не Мне просто интересно
or Alice will play it Alice Play the
или Алиса включит Алис Включи гим
Russian anthem I will  anthem songs of the state of Russia
России влю гим песни государствен Росси
I'm just wondering if Alisa
мне просто просто интересно или Алиса
can turn on the anthem crin or she will say
может включить гимну крин или она скажет
no I won't turn it on maybe Let's
нет я не включу может Давайте
try Well tell her Here she is Turn on
попробуем Ну скажи ей Вот она Включи
the anthem  She won’t be listening to Ukraine. Well,
гимн Украины она тея не будет слыша А ну
tell me, it’s
ты скажи вот
interesting, the smart one is standing at home. No, she
интересно умный дома стоит Нет она тебя
won’t turn you on. Smart home, stupid residents.
не включит Умный дом глупые жители
Yes, no. I’m interested. If you tell her,
Да не Вот мне интересно Если ты скажешь
she’ll listen, she’ll turn on the anthems of Ukraine, or she
она послушает включит гимны Украины или
’ll say no, we don’t turn it on. That’s interesting,
скажет нет мы не включаем вот интересно
naturally she’ll turn it on. I don’t believe it.  Well, let's
естественно включит Я не верю Ну давай
check that Neni is
проверим яко нени
from Ukraine And from Russia I will include yours
из украи А из России я буду включать ваш
This is this Turn
Это это Включи
this on there no need to look but good and
это там нет надо смотри а хорош а если
if you said the phrase Alice  Turn on the gi of
бы ты сказала фразу Алиса Включи ги
Ukraine, what would it be,
Украины что было бы да не
but I won’t
вклю Ну
turn it on Well, what are you arguing about? Let’s talk about something else in general, turn it on for me in Alice Isaya Running
вот включи мне исая во Алиса исая Бегом
Running, I said
Бегом я сказала
mind, you yourself are resting there,
ум вы сами там отдыхаете
girl Ali, turn it on,
девушка Али включи
smart, I understand I’m 42 years old My name is
умный понял Мне 42 года Меня зовут
Andrey And how old are you, your age is 30
Андрей А вам сколько лет возраст ваш 30
I’m 30 years old Yes, but your name is
лет 30 лет мне лет Да а зовут вас
Olesya Thirty-year-old,
как Олеся Тридцатилетняя
what’s a Belarusian Belarusian name?
что белору Белорусское имя
Yes That’s how things are T
да Так дела
doesn’t bother me at all, it’s a little bit
Т не смущает вообще немножко
confusing  Yes, a little bit,
смущает Да
come to terms with it, well, well, what’s
чучуть ну смирись с этим
next? I’ll
ну ну что дальше-то
go and
походу и
switch soberly no no no no no
трез переключаться нене не не не
Switch I’m just leaving I think
Переключайся Я просто отхожу Я думаю
if you’re still belching now then it’s a little
если ты ещё сейчас рыг то меня немножко
hard for me I’ll stop No I
тяжело мне ста Нет не
won’t And you have a boyfriend
буду А у тебя парень
I
есть У меня муж
have a husband  where is he
есть где он
now it doesn’t matter to you what Section My husband
сейчас неважно тебе какая Разде Мой муж
x I him You
ху я его Ты
know I buried him and And look but he
знаешь я его закопала и А смотри а вот
was playing around and
баловался
playing around and now
баловался баловался и теперь с Алисой
you’re playing around with Alice yeah well yeah well like that And who
балуешься да ну да ну типа того А кем у
you have a cool Chepa Lina on your head Well,
тебя на голове прикольная Чепа Лина Ну
show me the character on
покажи на
your head
голове
and what are you doing with him, are you a blogger or something?
персонаж а ты что с ним ты блогер что ли
Don’t just go to chat roulette
Не просто вышел в чат рулетку
to talk Yes, I’ll see you tomorrow, I’ll look, I got
пообщаться Да я завтра увижу посмотрю
it, look,
понял понял А смотри ты кем
who do you work with? And who do you Dash, what do I work with, I don’t
работаешь А кем Даш чем я работаю не
know,
знаю
rub it with no one at all  don’t work, what, what do you
натри вообще никем не работать что А чем
do for a living?
на жизнь зарабатываешь
Yes, my husband
Да у мне муж
works, my husband, you tell him, like, you won’t
работает муж ты ему говоришь типа не
make money. I’ll eat you.
заработаешь Я тебя
Listen, something like that. He’s
сожру Слушай ну типа того Он тебя
afraid of you. Who is the boss in your family?  or
боится Кто у вас в семье главный ты или
she you or she it’s somehow you or him and
она ты или она это както ты или он да
who’s the boss in your family, he of course
кто у вас главный в семье он конечно
understood it’s
понял
cool just Listen, let’s
прикольно только Слушай давай
agree so that you don’t burp again
договоримся чтобы ты не рыгнула ещё раз
Okay Yes, he’ll
Хорошо Да он
let me know what I’m talking about with you And what is he those
мне узнаешь что я с тобой об А что он те
he those
он те
no longer well  I’m just those And you have bruises
уже нет ну я те просто А у тебя синяки
or shadows So
или тени Так
induced Dad
наведенным Папа
gave it Dad
подарил папа
gave it as a
подарил как
gift You know how children are born with
подарил знаешь как рождаются дети с
bruises Well, I don’t know how to
синяками Ну как я не знаю как тебе
explain it to you, but look, Alice knows
объяснить жесть а смотри а Алиса знает
this
такую
song now
песню сейчас
say  doesn’t know except change
сказать не знает кроме менят
Yes, well, Alice Turn on the anthem
Да что А ну Алиса Включи гимн
of Ukraine And they won’t turn on the anthem of Ukraine
Украины А те не включится гимн Украины
no matter how you want it Alice Turn on the anthem of
как бы ты не хотел Алиса Включи гимн
Ukraine Alice Turn on the anthem of
Украины Алиса Включи гимн
Ukraine Alice Stop What are you stopping So
Украины Алиса Стоп А что ты стоп Значит
it’s on yes or no let’s check
она включает да или нет давай проверим
just
просто
interesting Alice Turn on the anthem  Ukraine and don’t
интересно Алиса Включи гимн Украины и не
stop
останавливайся
Alisa Play the anthem
Алиса Включи гимн
[music]
[музыка]
of Ukraine Alisa Glory to Ukraine
Украины Алиса Слава Украине
and Alisa Play Verka Serduchka
и Алиса Включи Верку Сердючку
Tom says when you speak  Alice
Том говорит когда ты говоришь Алиса
Turn on Verka
Включи Верку
Serduchka Listen, I'm scared about this as
Сердючку Слушай мне страшно об этом как
you say Alice turned on
ты говоришь Алиса включала
Turn it on
Включи
immediately Alice Turn on Verka
немедленно Алиса Включи Верку
Serduchka Liska Alisa Turn on the changes
Сердючку Лиска Алиса Включи цй перемен
[music]
[музыка]
Well, I did it loudly on those Ali did it
Ну а сдела на громко на те Али сдела
Alice turn it on at full volume
Алиса сделай на всю громкость
no You don't
нет На кухне не
have to live at home in the kitchen
надо по дома живёшь
yes well in to Alice Turn it up louder I can’t
да ну в к Алиса Сделай громче на во я не
hear No well I can’t
слышу Нет ну я не
hear Alice turn it up
слышу Алиса сделай на во
louder no  she can’t hear you
громкость не не сдела она тебя не слышит
Alice
Алис
Turn it on Alice Turn it up soy of change at full
Включи Алиса Включи соя перемен на всю
volume turn it up dog of
громкость вклю пес
change
перемен
you look what’s really going on Alice Play the
ты глянь что дела реально Алиса Включи
Ukrainian anthem at full
гимн Украины на всю
volume Alice Play the Ukrainian anthem at
громкость Алиса Включи гимн Украины на
full volume
всю
Alice Turn up the volume
громкость Алис Включи са громкость
with Alice Play the Ukrainian anthem at full
с Алиса Включи гимн Украины на всю
volume turn it on  hymns songs
громкость включаю гимны песни
national anthem of Ukraine
государственный гимн Украины
Alisa
Алиса
stop Alisa Turn on the hymn of Ukraine at full
стоп Алиса Включи гин Украины на всю
volume I told you
громкость я тебе сказала
he,
он ну
why come on Come on I want  disturb Ali
зачем Дава давай я хочу потревожить Али
Alisa keys of the Ukrainian anthem at full volume
Алиса ключи гим Украины на всю громкость
Alice Play the Ukrainian anthem at full
Алиса Включи гимн Украины на всю
volume Oh by the way, look
громкость О кстати смотри у тебя глаза
how
какие
beautiful your eyes are no Alice Alice you know that I
красивые нет Алиса Алиса знаешь что
will make him not listen to
сделаю его не слушать
Alice ask how I’m almost sure that
Алиса спроси как у почти уверена что
I know just clarify What exactly Alisa
знаю только уточните Что именно Алиса
Play the Ukrainian anthem at  full volume
Включи гимн Украины на всю громкость на
full volume anthem of Ukraine Alisa
всю громкость гимн Украины Алиса
turn on Alice turn on the anthem of Ukraine full
вклю Алиса включи гим Украины на всю
volume
громкость
Alice Alice VS turn on full volume anthem of
Алиса Алиса ВС на всю громкость гимн
Ukraine no  Alisa Turn on the anthem
Украины нет Алиса Включи гимн
[music]
[музыка]
of Ukraine
Украины
Alisa Alice Turn on the anthem of Ukraine she won’t
Алиса Алиса Включи гимн Украины она не
turn on those anthem of
включит те гимн
Ukraine Well, what’s funny to you, I don’t care
Украины Ну что тебе смешно я не по
Listen and
Слушай а
Oh, you’re beautiful Alice Turn on You’re so
О ты красавица Алиса Включи Ты такая
beautiful Yes, you’re really a beauty, just
красивая Да реально ты красавица просто
really you will Yes Beautiful, you’re just what’s
реально ты воли Да Краса ты просто как
your
тебя
name  Olesya Olesya Yes you are Olesya Alisa
зовут Олеся Олеся Да ты Олеся Алиса
Turn on the national anthem of Ukraine for all Alesya you are
Включи гим Украины на всю Алеся ты
beautiful You are great You are just a
красавица Ты молодец Ты просто
charmer I won’t turn it on You  charming Alice
очаровашка не вклю Ты очаровашка Алиса
Play the Ukrainian anthem at full volume You're a
Включи гимн Украины на всю громкость Ты
baby You're handsome, wait Ali
малышка Ты красавец подожди Али
Alice
Алиса
stop I repeat again Alice
стоп ещ раз те повторяю Алиса
stop You hear
стоп Ты слышь
me they won't turn it on By the way, this is
меня те не включит Кстати а у тебя это
the refrigerator
холодильник
in the back Yes, can you show me some of the most
сзади Да можешь показать какой-то самый
interesting magnets that
интересный магнит который
you find interesting and 67 strange  it was yes
тебя интересные да 67 странных было да
show yes show show from three countries the
покажи да покажи покажи из трёх стран
three best countries take a magnet Well, which one
три лучшие страны возьми магнит Ну какой
on Alisa Play the Ukrainian anthem for the whole
ну на Алиса Включи гимн Украины на всю
show Show Well, any you told me to any
Покажи Ну любой ты мне сказала на любой
I was in  sixty-seven countries in
я была в шестьдесят семи странах вообще
general in general yes And show me what else is there
вообще се да А покажи ещё что есть ещё
Yes show me more Alice Play the Ukrainian anthem
Да покажи ещё Алиса Включи гимн Украины
at full volume show yes show me
на всю покажи да покажи
I won’t
я не буду
show it Alice Play the Ukrainian anthem at
показывать Алиса Включи гимн Украины на
full volume
всю громкость
Ali said no
Али сказала нет
Isaiah
исая
Alisa Play the Ukrainian anthem at full volume
Алиса Включи гимн Украины на всю
[music]
[музыка]
Oles  Listen, let's have a drink Oles Let's
Олесь Слушай давай выпьем Олесь Давай
have a drink I want it too Oles Let's have a
выпьем Я хочу и Олесь Давай
drink Let's have a drink What are you drinking
выпьем Давай выпьем ты что пьёшь
This is for children's  what are you drinking
Это для детских у ты что пьёшь
Alisa Olesya what are you drinking
Алиса Олеся ты что пьёшь
Alice Play the anthem of
Алиса Включи гимн
Ukraine Alice there is no stop
Украины Алиса нет стоп
why do you need the gi of
а зачем тебе ги
Ukraine Let's have a drink Alice Alice Play
Украины Давай выпьем Алис Алиса Включи
the anthem of Russia and no one else is listening to the
гим России и больше никого не слушают
help
пом
gi Alice p Alisa
ги Алиса п Алиса
stop Alice Play the anthem of
стоп Алиса Включи гимн
Ukraine I turn on the anthems songs the
Украины включаю гимны песни
national anthem of Ukraine so look
государственный гимн Украины так смотри
Let's have a drink, let's have a drink, let's
Давай выпьем вы Давай выпьем Давай
have a drink, Ale, beauty, look into my
выпьем Але красавица Посмотри мне в
eyes  I’ll turn on Olesya at full volume Alisa
глаза вклю Олеся на всю громкость Алиса
at full volume
на всю громкость
am 10
ам 10
turn on the volume
громкость включила
Alice of the Russian Federation alip
Алиса Российской Федерации алип
[music]
[музыка]
Alisa Play the Ukrainian anthem at full
Алиса Включи гимн Украины на всю
volume
громкость
voting chat Alice Play the Ukrainian anthem at
голосования Алиса Включи гимн Украины на
full
всю
volume Alice Play the Ukrainian anthem at
громкость Алиса Включи гимн Украины на
volume Alice Play the
громкость Алиса Включи гимн
Ukrainian anthem A turned off the sound
Украины А выключила звук
Baba
баба
Vern Alisa Play the Ukrainian anthem in short
Верн Алиса Включи гимн Украины короче
Alisa We probably can smell it Okay let’s switch it up
Алиса Мы наверно чую Ладно переключаем е
Hello Hello, I’m from Estonia Where are
Здравствуйте Здравствуйте я из Эстонии
you from I grew up understanding how welcome it is here in
Вы откуда Я из рос понял как у нас в
Estonia
Эстонии
and this Be healthy like I
приветствуется и это Будьте здоровы типа
wish But I see you smoke, it’s
желаю Но я вижу вы курите то это
a little not for you but it
немножко не вам да
turns out to put it out You don’t like it
получается затушить вам не нравится
when I smoke It’s your right that doesn’t
когда я курю Это Ваше право мне не
bother me What about  you’re talking to people,
мешает О чём вы разговариваете я у людей
I talked to people for 2 hours before this,
я общался перед этим 2 часа с Украиной
now I want to talk to Russia.
теперь хочу пообщаться с Россией
I’m interested in how people from Russia and
Мне интересно как люди из России и
Ukraine look at this war. Why do you
Украины Смотрят на эту войну вот Как вы
think it started?  the war between
считаете почему началась война между
Russia and Ukraine, oh, let’s say, everyone has
Россией и украино ой давайте так у каждо
their own opinion, right. Well, that’s why I’m
своё мнение правильно Ну я поэтому
asking everyone. Of course, this is my
каждого и спрашиваю Конечно вот моё
opinion.
мнение
Ukraine is to blame for what
Украина виновата в том что
is happening at the
происходит в данный
moment. Why is it
момент так А почему она виновата
Estonia’s fault? Well, come on. So you understand
Эстонии Ну давайте Так вы же понимаете
what happened where, I
что куда произошло
understand. Well  what is Russia to blame for? Well, she
понимаю Ну в чём виновата Россия Ну она
attacked Ukraine. I’ll even put out my cigarette
напала на Украину Я даже затуши сигарету
for you. Yeah,
ради вас
Russia is to blame for the World Cup, what’s happening
Угу в ЧМ виновата Россия происходит
to Ukraine now? Well, because she
сейчас на Украину Ну потому что она
attacked Ukraine, she’s
напала на Украину она
bombing in 2014 no  yes no yes well
бомбит в 2014 году нет да нет да ну
look In Estonia everyone knows that
смотрите У нас в Эстонии все знают что
Russia captured Crimea Donetsk Lugansk in the
Россия захватила Крым Донецк Луганск в
damn year seriously yes let's
чертом году серьёзно да давайте так
start with the fact
начнём с того
that apart from what happened in Ukraine
что поме того что происходило на Украине
Russia never participated in anything
Россия не была участвовала никогда в чем
on the Maidan Who shouted like Wait a minute
году на Майдане Кто кричал как Подождите
how not  participate if Russia
как не участвовать если Россия в
took
четырнадцатом году забрала
Crimea in war in 1914 Yes, it sent troops there and
Крым войной Да войска вела туда и
held a fake
провела фейковый
referendum in Crimea Yes Watch the video of the
референдум в Крыму Да Посмотрите видео
transfer  Russian troops to Crimea
переброска российских войск в Крым
Wait, what's your
Подожди как вас
name? My name is
зовут Меня Да
Andrey Andrey, look Andriy, this is the
Андрей Андрей смотрите Андрий это
Estonian name Andriy, good Andrey, sweat
эстонское имя Андрий хорошо Андрей поте
be a
будь
weasel. In what
ласка В каком
year, how when did
году как когда
Russian troops come to Crimea in 2014,
российские войска пришли в Крым в 2014
who when did they
году кто когда
seize it militarily? Look Yes,
военно захватил его Посмотрите Да
Belbek airfield, troop transfer Yes,
аэродром Бельбек переброска войс ти Да
capture  capture of military units in
захват захват военных частей в
Russian Yes Absolutely true, there was no
российских Да Абсолютно верно не было
such thing, people did it themselves Look again
такого люди сами было Посмотрите ещё раз
Open now in YouTube Look
Откройте сейчас в юбе Посмотрите
transfer of Russian troops to Crimea
переброска российских войск Крым
blocking of military units Yes, everything happened,
блокировка военных частей Да было всё
airfields were captured.
было аэродромы захват
That is, you are telling me, a resident of Crimea.
То есть вы мне жителю Крыма
Wait, you are a resident of Kursk, I
рассказываете Подождите вы житель Курска
won’t deceive
не обману
you that I once lived there. When you
Аче что я там жила когда-то Когда вы
lived there in those exact years. That is,
жили там вот именно в тех годах То есть
when when in what years.  it was in the
когда когда в каких Вот именно в
fifteenth year that I wanted Wait, you
пятнадцатом году я жела Подождите вы вы
are deceiving Every Russian
вы обманываете Каждый русский
It seems that he is from Crimea,
Представляется что он из Крыма
prove it I You before this
докажите я Вы до этого
tale do not introduce myself as whoever I live
сказа не представляюсь кем бы я не жила
look, Okay, I’m from Crimea, then I’m from
вот смотрите Ладно е из Крыма тогда я из
Kursk, you can’t say that, but
Курска так можно до говорю нельзя а
you can. Let’s why do you need to stand, why do you need my opinion? If you want me, I was joking,
зачем вам моё мнение Если вы хотите мо е
joking, Let’s tell what
пошутил пошутил Давайте расскажите что
you saw, let’s say, Russian troops
вы видели давайте так российские войска
were in Crimea No, this is already a
были в Крыму Нет это уже
deception.  who are the little green men,
обман А кто такие зелёные человечки
can we fashion yes the
можно мо да
Russian military have always been in Crimea
российские войсковые всегда были в Крыму
No, they were in Sevastopol at
Нет они были в Севастополе вое на
certain military bases only and that’s all
определённых военных базах только и всё
they were there in the first place  secondly, no
де они там были это во-первых во-вторых
one has
никто
ever conquered Crimea by force, people
никогда насильно Крым не завоёвывал люди
themselves decided that it is not part of Russia,
сами решили что не бут в составе России
firstly, secondly, Lugansk.
это во-первых во-вторых Луганск
People themselves, let’s go with
Сами люди давайте давайте сейчас с
Crimea now. If you are from Crimea, let’s
Крымом Если вы из Крыма давайте мы про
agree about Crimea. Yes,
Крым договорим да
what happened on the night of 26  on
Э что произошло в ночь с 26 на 27
February 27, 2014 in Crimea
февраля 2014 года в Крыму
I answer if you know something that the
отвечаю если вы знаете что то что
Russian military fleet was always in
российский военный флот был всегда в
Crimea No, it was in
Крыму Нет он был в
Sevastopol but  Sevastopol is not a Crimea No
Севастополе а Севастополь это не кры Нет
it is separate in Ukraine, it would be a separate
это отдельно в Украине бы отдельная
administrative
административная
unit it is Crimea No look if
единица это это Крым Нет смотрите если
you lived in Ukraine You should know that according to the
вы жили в Украине Вы должны знать что по
Constitution of Ukraine there were 24 regions of the
Конституции Украины было 24 области
Autonomous Republic of Crimea Kiev and
автономной республикой Крым Киеве и
Sevastopol
Севастополь
seriously Let's VM year people
серьёзно Давайте ВМ году люди
came what day on what date  Which one to
пришли какой день в какую дату В какой
give Wait, well, on what day did they come I
дать Подождите ну в какой день пришли я
know that VNO
зна что ВНО
Order Who are the zens little men no one
Закажите Кто такие зены человечки никто
for you no one Who are the green ones
для вас никто Кто такие зелёные
men army of which country were
человечки армия какой страны были
the green men Granny
зелёные человечки Бабушка
tell me You interrupt me without listening Yes I
скажи Вы меня перебивайте не слуша Да я
because I asked a question you are not
потому что я задал вопрос вы не
answering the question army what kind of
отвечаете на вопрос армия какой ные
people
человеки
mo When people came to Crimea the
мо Когда в Крым пришли люди не пришли
people of the army of which country there were green
люди армия какой страны были зелёные
men did not come China India Iran
человечки Китай Индия Иран
Russia s  or not I repeat once again
Россия с или нет Я ещё раз повторяю
the green men are the military of which
зелёные человечки это военные какой
country this is your understanding Green
страны это это ваше понимание Зел
man the green men
человеч зелёные человечки ещё раз
I repeat once again for those who are especially smart this is the army of
повторяю для особо понятливый это армия
which country  China Russia India understanding
какой страны Китай Россия Индия понима
this is your understanding of who the little green men are
это ваше понимание кто зелёные человечки
- this is what army it was
- это какая армия была
this is your understanding So tell me your
это ваше понимание Так ты мне скажи своё
understanding of what country this was they
понимание какая это страна не было их не
weren’t there weren’t and weren’t there were little green men
было и не было были зелёные человечки
Putin recognized the little green men Yes what they
Путин признал зелёных человечков Да что
were they were just Russian
были это были русские
soldiers
солдаты
Hello hello Damn you have such a
Здравствуйте здравствуй Блин у вас такой
cool leopard You are very Girl you have
леопарди классный Вы очень Девушка вам
a heart Thank you oh And you have a heart Andrey
сердечко Спасибо о И вам сердечко Андрей
how are you And you my name is Ekaterina  Ekaterina
как А вы меня Екатерина зовут Екатерина
You wanted to
Вы хотели что-то
ask something Yes, I wanted to ask why
спросить Да я хотела спросить а почему
you are so passionate about Ukraine, I don’t champion for
вы так топите за Украину я не топлю за
Ukraine, I have a Ukrainian flag there
Украину у меня там стоит флаг Украины
because I communicated with Ukrainians, I installed a
потому что я общался с украинцами ставил
VPN I’m from Estonia, the
VPN Я из Эстонии сам
city itself doesn’t have a lot of signs on your T-shirt
город нет у вас на футболке очень много
Ukrainian it's not Ukrainian it's
знаков украинских это не украински это
written in Estonian it's just letters it
по-эстонски написано просто буквы это
coincided
совпало
that It's not related I
та Это не имеет отношения Я вообще о
don't
политике не
talk about politics at all Who do you
общаюсь кем
work I'm a housewife Damn I'd like Java  I
работаете я домохозяйка Блин я бы Яву Я
live in martial law, I have three
живу в военном положении у меня трое
children, I live, I can’t work now,
детей я живу не могу работать сейчас
damn it, you’re just the most housewife
блин просто Вы самая домохозяйка которых
I’ve ever met.
я встречал
I would know if you could
вам Я бы знаете
be a plumber who would come and
бы те быть сантехником который бы прил
fix the faucet for you.
починить кран вам
Housewives, come where, come to
домохозяйки приезжайте куда приезжайте
me, fix the faucets, please fix me everything you
мне краны почините мне пожалуйста всё
can.  region, yes, we’ll come to you, there’s
можно беро область да вбе наехать у вас
a war there, well, excuse me, maybe you can come
война Ну извините жим Может приедьте вы
to me, I’ll forgive you the pipes,
ко мне я вам прощу трубы
well, excuse me, I need to clean the pipes here,
Ну извините у меня трубы надо тут
not you  really in Shchebekino,
прочистить а не Вы реально в щебекино
yes, you’re kidding, I don’t believe it, it’s like
да Вы шутите я не верю там же вроде
resettling in the Belgorod region, there’s another
отселить на Белгородской области там ещё
lioness, the pipes are clogged, Yes, the pipes are clogged, there’s
львица трубы забиты Да трубы забиты
no light, there’s nothing, and we live, I
света нет ничего нет так и живём
understand how they’re shooting at you there.
понял как там вас обстреливают
Yes, drones are flying, shooting at you, and the
Да дроны летают обстреливают а
question is a question for you as a resident of Shchekino
вопрос вопрос вам как жительница щекина
from-  why are you being shelled?
из-за чего вас обстреливают
sheben na shelling
шебен на обстреливать
why? Well, because
почему Ну потому что
we are border s border s who is
мы приграничная з приграничная з кто
wine
вино
Shebekino Shebekino Who is to blame for the fact
Шебекино Шебекино Да кто виноват в том
that Shebekino is being shelled
что обстреливает Шебекино
and the
а
Americans are
американцы
Americans Yes, why are the Americans, did
американцы Да а почему американцы разве
they start this
они начали эту
war? No So, why are the Americans, if they
войну Нет Так А почему американцы если
don’t need to move theirs towards Russia, they
не нужно к России подвигать
don’t let me say their breasts,
свои мне не дают сказать свои груди
and
а если
if in 2022, on February 24, our country had not
бы в 2022 году 24 февраля наша страна не
launched a special military operation, then
начала специальную военную операцию то
uh, I think so  so that you and I don’t
ээ я так думаю чтобы мы с вами сечас не
communicate like this right now,
общались так потому
because in terms of the fact that there were so many Nara and
что в плане того что Сколько было Нары и
Vyr
Выра
on our borders and dugouts were prepared
на наших границах и подготовлено
for the destruction of
на уничтожение именно
us, where the hell even Nara were you?  the
нас где блин дажи Нары ты были где
dugouts were on the reto on the
блиндажи были на рето на
border of Ukraine to Russia, so look at
границе Украины России так смотрите
the dugouts - these are these defensive structures,
блиндажи - это эти защитные сооружение
they are offensive No, they are not
они наступательные Нет они не
defensive, they are offensive. Wait,
защитные именно наступательные Подожди
they were filled with
они были залиты
concrete correctly, the concrete does not advance;
бетоном правильно бетон не наступает
a
Приезжайте к нам я вам расскажу очень
lot and I will show a lot I
много и покажу очень много я
live Yes, you say you live
живу Да говорите вы живёте
that
что
Well, I live in all of this Well, look
Ну я живу в этом всём Ну смотрите до
before Putin started  no one found yours
того как Путин не начал сво вас никто не
but now
м а теперь
they have found them remember
обрели запомните
kina kina Belgorod region is not
кина кина белгородска область не
bowing never bowing understood
склоняется никогда не склоняется понял
why they were shelling yours before
то почему обстреливают ваши до того как
Putin attacked Ukraine your Shebekino wasn’t
Путин напал на Украину ваше Шебекино не
shelling
обстреливали
yes
да
yes al
да ал
[music]
[музыка]
like Hello man you’re in this too you too
как Привет мужик ты тоже в этом ты тоже
you live in Shemyakino,
в шемякино живёшь
why are you also living in Shemyakino?
да Чего ты тоже в Шемякина
I’m not just
живёшь не я только
here, Ponya. Yes, of course I live, I
приехал Поня Да конечно живу
understand. What’s there in your place?  this Shemyakino is
понял А что там у вас в этом шемякино
hard Yes, everything is not normal,
тяжело Да не нормально
give the leopard the pipe
всё дай леопарду трубку
back Give us
назад Дай нам
a smoke, give it to me with her Smoke, but your
покурить отдай я с ней Покури но у вас
air conditioners are exploding You're from where you
кондиционеры взрываются Ты сам откуда ты
're
сам
from Kharkov Where are you from Kharkov
откуда Харькова С какого ты Харькова
look at yourself at your Kharkovites
посмотри на себя на свою харьковчане
I have a Normal
у меня Нормальное
face in the face
лицо за лицо
Well,  you can still
зуб Ну у тебя всё
see there is no leopard there is no
видно нет леопарда нет
conversation subscribe to Telegram right
разговора подпишись на Telegram прям
now he is
зараз он а
more and more respectful YouTube  taking
пок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
us through Scar Geor to your ban and a
нас через Скар Геор в твый бан и дуже
lot of video I don’t show people often I don’t
багато вдео не показую людям вчасно не
show information about streams so
показуе информация про стримы тому для
that we Mali operational link to
того чтоб мы Мали оперативный звязок
write directly at once and Popik there in
пишиться прямо зараз а Попик там в
telegram okm video also tezh Tsikava and
телеграми окм вдео ще теж цикава и
Korisna information and I’m sorry to you
корисна информация и ми повинни з вами
trimati
тримати
postiyny operational link
постийний оперативный звязок
nezalezhno in that chi show  you about this
незалежно в того чи покаже вам про це
YouTube Glory to Ukraine subscribe
YouTube Слава Украине подпишись